Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 22: Star Staff Negatives and Prints, 1899-1966
  - Staff - Mu-Rn, Undated (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Staff - Ro-V, Undated (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Staff - W-Z, Undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Prints, Undated (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Series 23: Photograph Morgue
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical
    - Aaker - Ababio (Collective Folders: A; AB; ABA) (Box 0001)
    - Abba - Abernathy, Margaret (Dr) (Collective Folders: ABD; ABE; ABEL; ABER) (Box 0002)
    - Abernathy, Ralph D. (Rev) - Abrams (Collective Folders: ABR; ABRAH; ABRAM; ABRAMS) (Box 0003)
    - Abrassimov - Achinstein (Collective Folders: ABS; AC; ACH; ACK) (Box 0004)
    - Acker, Sharon - Adams, Don (Collective Folders: ACKERMAN; AD; ADAIR; ADAM; ADAMS A; ADAMS B; ADAMS C; ADAMS D) (Box 0005)
    - Adams, Donald - Adams, Ray (Collective Folders: ADAMS E; ADAMS F; ADAMS G; ADAMS H; ADAMS J; ADAMS K; ADAMS L; ADAMS N; ADAMS M; ADAMS O; ADAMS P; ADAMS Q; ADAMS R) (Box 0006)
    - Adams, Sam - Adenauer (Collective Folders: ADAMS S; ADAMS T; ADAMS U-V.; ADAMS W; ADAMS X-Z) (Box 0007)
    - Adelberg - Afshar (Collective Folders: ADE; ADEL; ADK; ADL; ADO; AE; AF; AG) (Box 0008)
    - Agah - Agnew, Spiro T. (Collective Folders: AGE; AGN) (Box 0009)
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box 0010)
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box 0011)
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box 0012)
    - Agnew, Spiro T. - Aherne (Collective Folders: AGU; AH; AHE) (Box 0013)
    - Ahidjo - Akeman (Collective Folders: AI; AIK; AIL; AIT; AJ; AK) (Box 0014)
      General
      Willie Mays Aikens folder missing label
    - Akers- Albert, Carl (Collective Folders: AKER; AKH; AKI; AL; ALA; ALAN; ALB; ALBA; ALBERT) (Box 0015)
    - Albert, Carl (Mrs. and Family) - Alden (Collective Folders: ALBR; ALBRIGHT; ALC; ALD; ALDE) (Box 0016)
    - Alderman - Alexander.Clifford, Jr. (Collective Folders: ALDRI; ALDR; ALE; ALES; ALEX; ALEXANDER A-D) (Box 0017)
    - Alexander, Denise - Al-Gosaibi (Collective Folders: ALEXANDER E-H; ALEXANDER I-L; ALEXANDER M-P; ALEXANDER R-Z; ALF) (Box 0018)
    - Alhegelan - Allbritton (Collective Folders: ALG; ALI; ALL; ALLAN; ALLAR) (Box 0019)
    - Allen - Allen, George (Collective Folders: ALLE; ALLEN A; ALLEN B; ALLEN C; ALLEN D; ALLEN E; ALLEN F; ALLEN G) (Box 0020)
    - Allen, George (Mrs. and Family) - Allen, Marty (Collective Folders: ALLEN H; ALLEN I; ALLEN J; ALLEN K; ALLEN L; ALLEN M) (Box 0021)
    - Allen, Mel - Allende (Collective Folders: ALLEN N; ALLEN O; ALLEN P; ALLEN Q; ALLEN R; ALLEN S; ALLEN T; ALLEN U; ALLEN V; ALLEN W) (Box 0022)
    - Allende - Allyson (Collective Folders: ALLEN X-Z; ALLG; ALLI; ALLISON A-J; ALLISON K-Q; ALLISON R-Z; ALLM; ALLS; ALLY) (Box 0023)
    - Almada- Alpert (Collective Folders: ALP; ALO; ALS; ALM) (Box 0024)
      Torn label for Allenson, Gary
    - Al-Sabah - Alvarez (Collective Folders: ALT; ALTE; ALTM; ALU; ALV; ALVA) (Box 0025)
      Almon, Bill no label
    - Alverez - Ames (Collective Folders: AM; AMA; AMB; AME; AMBR) (Box 0026)
    - Amies - Anastasi, Joseph (Collective Folders: AMES; AMI; AMM; AMO; AN) (Box 0027)
    - Anastasi, Joseph F. - Anderson, Donna (Collective Folders: ANA; ANDE; ANDERSON A; ANDERSON B; ANDERSON C; ANDERSON D) (Box 0028)
    - Anderson, Donny - Anderson, John B. (Rep) (Collective Folders: ANDERSON E; ANDERSON F; ANDERSON G; ANDERSON H; ANDERSON I; ANDERSON J) (Box 0029)
    - Anderson, John B. (Rep) - Anderson, Robert B. (Collective Folders: ANDERSON K; ANDERSON L; ANDERSON M; ANDERSON N; ANDERSON O; ANDERSON P; ANDERSON Q; ANDERSON R) (Box 0030)
    - Anderson, Robert B. - Andretti (Collective Folders: ANDERSON S; ANDERSON T; ANDERSON V; ANDERSON W) (Box 0031)
    - Andrews- Andrews, Tod (Collective Folders: ANDREW A-Z; ANDREWS A-E; ANDREWS F-J; ANDREWS K-O; ANDREWS P-Z) (Box 0032)
    - Andrews, Tina - Ankrah (Collective Folders: ANDRO; ANDRU; ANG; ANGEL; ANGELO; ANGL; ANN) (Box 0033)
    - Ann-Margret - Anstett (Collective Folders: ANO; ANS) (Box 0034)
      Annenberg, Walter- no label
    - Antell - Aparicio (Collective Folders: ANT; ANTHONY A-J; ANTHONY K-O; ANTHONY P-Z; ANTI; ANTO; ANTOINE; ANZ; AP) (Box 0035)
    - Apke - Araki (Collective Folders: APO; APPE; APPLE; APR; APT; AQ; AR; ARA; ARAG) (Box 0036)
    - Aramburu - Arenales (Collective Folders: ARAN; ARB; ARCH; ARCHER; ARCHIBALD A-Z; ARD; ARE) (Box 0037)
    - Arends - Armas (Collective Folders: ARG; ARI; ARK; ARL; ARM; ARMA) (Box 0038)
    - Armistead - Armstrong, Neil (Collective Folders: ARME; ARMI; ARMO; ARMSTRONG; ARMSTRONG A-E; ARMSTRONG F-J; ARMSTRONG K-O) (Box 0039)
    - Armstrong, Neil - Arnett, Alvin (Collective Folders: ARMSTRONG P-Z; ARN; ARNE) (Box 0040)
    - Arnett, Edwin - Arrow (Collective Folders: ARNOLD A-G; ARNOLD H-P; ARNOLD R-Z; ARNS; ARO) (Box 0041)
    - Arroyo - Asencio (Collective Folders: ARR; ARS; ART; ARTE; ARTHUR; AS; ASA; ASC) (Box 0042)
    - Asgeirsson - Ashley, Silvia (Collective Folders: ASH; ASHB; ASHE) (Box 0043)
    - Ashley, Thomas - Astaire, Adele (Collective Folders: ASHLEY; ASHTON; ASK; ASS; ASP; AST) (Box 0044)
    - Astaire, Fred - Atkeson (Collective Folders: AT; ATCHISON; ATH) (Box 0045)
    - Atiyeh - Aubrey (Collective Folders: ATK; ATT; ATW; AU; AUB) (Box 0046)
    - Auchincloss - Austin, John (Collective Folders: AUD; AUE; AUG; AUSTAD; AUSTIN A-F; AUSTIN G-L) (Box 0047)
    - Austin, Pamela - Avery (Collective Folders: AUSTIN M-Q; AUSTIN R-Z; AV; AVE; AVERY) (Box 0048)
    - Avila - Azikiwe (Collective Folders: AW; AX; AY; AYD; AYERS; AYL) (Box 0049)
    - Aziz - Bach (Collective Folders: AZ; B; BAB; BABI; BAC;BACH) (Box 0050)
    - Bacharach - Badoglio (Collective Folders: BACK; BACON; BAD; BAE) (Box 0051)
    - Baer- Bailey, Consuelo (Collective Folders: BAG; BAH; BAI; BAIL; BAILEY A-D; BAILEY E-I) (Box 0052)
    - Bailey, Ed - Bain, Barbara (Collective Folders: BAILEY J; BAILEY K-M; BAILEY N-Q; BAILEY R; BAILEY S; BAILEY T-Z; BAIN) (Box 0053)
    - Bain, Conrad - Baker, Del (Collective Folders: BAIN; BAIR; BAK; BAKER A; BAKER B) (Box 0054)
    - Baker, Diane - Baker, Howard (Collective Folders: BAKER C; BAKER D; BAKER E; BAKER F; BAKER G; BAKER H) (Box 0055)
    - Baker, Irving - Baker, Tony (Collective Folders: BAKER I; BAKER J; BAKER K; BAKER L; BAKER M; BAKER O; BAKER P; BAKER Q; BAKER R; BAKER S; BAKER T; BAKER U) (Box 0056)
    - Baker, Wilson - Baldwin, Billy (Collective Folders: BAKER V; BAKER W; BAKER X Y Z; BAL; BALA; BALC; BALD; BALDWIN) (Box 0057)
    - Baldwin, Dave - Ball (Collective Folders: BALE; BALI; BALL; BALL A; BALL B; BALL C; BALL D; BALL E; BALL F; BALL G; BALL H; BALL I; BALL J; BALL K; BALL L; BALL M; BALL N; BALL O; BALL P; BALL Q; BALL R) (Box 0058)
    - Ballance - Baltz (Collective Folders: BALL S; BALL U; BALL V; BALL W; BALL X Y Z; BALLA; BALLARD; BALLE; BALLI; BALLO; BALO; BALS; BALT) (Box 0059)
    - Balukas - Banks, Ernie (Collective Folders: BAM; BAN; BANA; BANC; BAND; BANE; BANF; BANG; BANK; BANKS A-F) (Box 0060)
    - Banks, James - Barattieri (Collective Folders: BANKS G-L; BANKS M-R; BANKS S-W; BANKS XYZ; BAHN; BANO; BAP; BAR) (Box 0061)
    - Barazzuti - Bardin (Collective Folders: BARB; BARBE; BARBER; BARBI; BARBO; BARC) (Box 0062)
    - Bardot - Barker, Jess (Collective Folders: BARD; BARE; BARG; BARI; BARK) (Box 0063)
    - Barker, Kylene - Barnard (Collective Folders: BARKER; BARL; BARN; BARNARD) (Box 0064)
    - Barnes, Angela - Barnes, Michael (Collective Folders: BARNES A-D; BARNES E-I; BARNES J; BARNES K-Q) (Box 0065)
    - Barnes, Mike - Barr, Candy (Collective Folders: BARNES R; BARNES S-Z; BARNETT; BARNETT A-G; BARNETT H-O; BARNETT R-Z; BARNEY; BARNH; BARO; BARON A-Z) (Box 0066)
    - Barr, David - Barron, Carter (Collective Folders: BARRA; BARRE; BARRETT A-E; BARRETT J-Q; BARRETT R-Z; BARRI; BARRO; BARRON) (Box 0067)
    - Barron, Herman - Barry, Marion (Collective Folders: BARROW; BARRY) (Box 0068)
    - Barry, Marion - Bartels (Collective Folders: BARS; BART;BARTA) (Box 0069)
    - Bartelt - Barty (Collective Folders: BARTE; BARTH; BARTHE; BARTHO; BARTLETT A-F; BARTLETT; G-L; BARTLETT M-Q; BARTLETT R-Z; BARTO; BARTON; BARTR; BARTS) (Box 0070)
    - Bartzen - Basler (Collective Folders: BAS; BASE; BASH; BASLER) (Box 0071)
      Barzani and Basilio folders needs new label
    - Basov - Bates (Collective Folders: BASO; BASS A-Z; BASSETT; BASSI; BAST; BAT; BATC; BATE; BATES A-E; BATES F-J) (Box 0072)
    - Bates, L.C. - Bauer, Charles (Collective Folders: BATES K-Q; BATES R-Z; BATH; BATI; BATO; BATR; BATS) (Box 0073)
    - Bauer, Hane - Bautista (Collective Folders: BAUGH; BAUM; BAUMAN; BAUMANN; BAUMG; BAV) (Box 0074)
    - Bavasi - Bayh, Birch (Collective Folders: BAX; BAY; BAYE) (Box 0075)
    - Bayh, Birch (Mrs) - Beadle (Collective Folders: BAYL; BAYLOR; BAYN; BAZ; BE; BEACH; BEAD) (Box 0076)
    - Beagles - Beall, William (Collective Folders: BEAL; BEALE; BEALL) (Box 0077)
    - Beam - Bean, Thomas (Collective Folders: BEAM) (Box 0078)
    - Bear - Beatles (Collective Folders: BEAN; BEAR; BEAS; BEAT) (Box 0079)
    - Beatles - Beban (Collective Folders: BEATT; BEAU; BEAV; BEAZ) (Box 0080)
    - Becerra- Becker (Collective Folders: BECH; BECK A; BECK F-J; BECK K-P; BECK Q-Z; BECKER A-F; BECKER G-K; BECKER L-Q; BECKER R-Z) (Box 0081)
    - Beckers - Beecham (Collective Folders: BECKETT; BECKHAM; BECKL; BECKMAN; BECKW; BED; BEE) (Box 0082)
      Charles Beckwith needs label
    - Beemer - Begin (Collective Folders: BEER; BEG) (Box 0083)
    - Begin, Menehem (Menachem) - Belafonte (Collective Folders: BEH; BEI; BEK; BEL; BELA) (Box 0084)
    - Belanger - Belieu (Collective Folders: BELC; BELF; BELG; BELI) (Box 0085)
    - Belin - Bell, John (Collective Folders: BELK; BELL; BELL A; BELL B; BELL C; BELL D; BELL E; BELL F; BELL G; BELL H; BELL I; BELL J) (Box 0086)
    - Bell, Lawrence - Bellmon (Collective Folders: BELL K; BELL L; BELL M; BELL N; BELL P; BELL Q; BELL R; BELL S; BELL T; BELL V; BELL W; BELL XYZ; BELLA; BELLE; BELLI) (Box 0087)
    - Bello - Bench (Collective Folders: BELLO; BELM; BELO; BELS; BELT; BEM; BEN) (Box 0088)
    - Benchley - Benitez (Collective Folders: BEND; BENE; BENI) (Box 0089)
    - Benjamin - Bennett, James (Collective Folders: BENJAMIN A-Z; BENN; BENNE; BENNETT A-C; BENNETT D-E; BENNETT F-I; BENNETT) (Box 0090)
    - Bennett, Joan - Bensinger (Collective Folders: BENNETT K-N; BENNETT O-P; BENNETT R; BENNETT S-V; BENNETT W; BENNETT X-Z; BENS) (Box 0091)
    - Benson - Benton (Collective Folders: BENSON A-J; BENSON K-Z; BENT; BENTLEY) (Box 0092)
    - Bentsen - Berendzen (Collective Folders: BENTON; BER; BERE; BERG) (Box 0093)
    - Berg - Bergheim (Collective Folders: BERGE; BERGEN; BERGER A-J; BERGER K-Q; BERGER R-Z; BERGH; BERGL) (Box 0094)
    - Bergland - Berla (Collective Folders: BERGM; BERI; BERK; BERL) (Box 0095)
    - Berle - Berman (Collective Folders: BERMAN; BERMAN A-G; BERMAN H-O; BERMAN P-Z; BERN) (Box 0096)
    - Bernadotte - Bernstein, Leonard (Collective Folders: BERNA; BERNARD; BERNE; BERNH; BERNI; BERNS; BERNSTEIN A; BERNSTEIN B-I) (Box 0097)
    - Bernstein, Leonard - Berry, E.Y. (Collective Folders: BERNSTEIN J-Q; BERNSTEIN R; BERNSTEIN S-Z; BERR; BERRY A-C; BERRY D; BERRY E; BERRY F-I; BERRY J ) (Box 0098)
    - Berry - Besson (Collective Folders: BERRY K-O; BERRY P-Q; BERRY R; BERRY S-Z; BERT; BERTI; BERS; BERTO; BESS) (Box 0099)
    - Best - Bevens (Collective Folders: BEST; BET; BETA; BETE; BETH; BETT; BETZ; BEU; BEV; BEVA; BEVE) (Box 0100)
    - Beveridge - Bibson (Collective Folders: BEVI; BEY A-Z; BEYE; BH; BI; BIA; BIAN; BIAS; BIB) (Box 0101)
    - Bibby - Biffle (Collective Folders: BIC; BID; BIE; BIEL; BIER; BIERE; BIG) (Box 0102)
    - Bigelow - Bing (Collective Folders: BIGGS A-Z; BIL; BILL; BILLI; BILLM; BIN; BIND; BING) (Box 0103)
    - Bingham - Bishara (Collective Folders: BINGHAM; BINH; BINK; BIR; BIRD A-E; BIRD F-J; BIRD K-O; BIRD P-Z; BIRDS) (Box 0104)
      Avis Birely needs label
    - Bishop - Bittman (Collective Folders: BIS; BISHOP A-B; BISHOP C; BISHOP D; BISHOP E-G; BISHOP H-I; BISHOP J; BISHOP K-O; BISHOP P-R; BISHOP S-V; BISHOP W; BISHOP XYZ; BISS; BIT; BITT) (Box 0105)
    - Bixby - Black, Karen (Collective Folders: BIX; BJ; BL; BLACK; BLACK A-C; BLACK D-G; BLACK H-J; BLACK K-N) (Box 0106)
    - Black, Kenny - Blackman, Joan (Collective Folders: BLACK O-R; BLACK S-Z; BLACKM) (Box 0107)
    - Blackmer -Blair, Linda (Collective Folders: BLACKW; BLAI; BLAIN; BLAIR) (Box 0108)
      black, rex and blaik, earl- needs new label
    - Blair, Montgomery - Blalock (Collective Folders: BLAK) (Box 0109)
    - Blanc - Blatchford, Joseph (Collective Folders: BLAN; BLANC; BLANCHARD; BLAND; BLANDFORD A-Z; BLANK; BLANKE; BLAS) (Box 0110)
    - Blatchford, Nicholas - Blitch (Collective Folders: BLAT; BLAU; BLE; BLEV; BLI; BLIGH A-Z; BLISS; BLIZ; BLO) (Box 0111)
    - Block - Blough (Collective Folders: BLOCH; BLOCK; BLOOD; BLOOM; BLOU) (Box 0112)
    - Blouin - Blumenthal, Charles (Collective Folders: BLU; BLUE; BLUM A-Z; BLUMBERG; BLUME; BLUMENFELD) (Box 0113)
    - Blumenthal, W. - Bochte (Collective Folders: BLUN; BLY; BO; BOAR; BOAT; BOB; BOBB; BOC) (Box 0114)
    - Bode - Boggs, T. (Collective Folders: BOD; BODE; BODI; BOE; BOEH; BOER; BOET; BOG; BOGA; BOGE; BOGG) (Box 0115)
    - Boggs, T. - Bok (Collective Folders: BOGL; BOHM; NOH; BOHR; BOI; BOK) (Box 0116)
    - Bokaska - Bolling, Spottswood (Collective Folders: BOL; BOLD; BOLE; BOLG; BOLI; BOLL) (Box 0117)
    - Bolling, Tiffany - Bond, Julian (Collective Folders: BOLT; BOM; BON; BOND) (Box 0118)
    - Bond, Langhorn - Bonzo (Collective Folders: BONE; BONN; BONO; BONS; BONT; BOO) (Box 0119)
    - Bookatz - Boorstin (Collective Folders: BOOK; BOONE; BOOTH) (Box 0120)
    - Booth - Borg, Bjorn (Collective Folders: BOR; BORD; BORE; BORG) (Box 0121)
    - Borg, Bjorn - Borman, Frank (Collective Folders: BORM) (Box 0122)
    - Borman, Frank - Bosley (Collective Folders: BORN; BORO; BORT; BOS) (Box 0123)
    - Bosman - Boudin (Collective Folders: BOST; BOSW; BOT; BOU) (Box 0124)
    - Boudreaux - Bovey (Collective Folders: BOUR; BOUS; BOV) (Box 0125)
    - Bowa - Bowles, Chester (Collective Folders: BOW; BOWD; BOWEN; BOWER; BOWI; BOWL; BOWLES) (Box 0126)
    - Bowles, Hargrove - Boyd, Gary (Collective Folders: BOWLING; BOWMAN A-I; BOWMAN J; BOWMAN K-Q; BOWAN R; BOWMAN S-Z; BOX; BOY; BOYCE; BOYD A-G; BOYD H-M) (Box 0127)
    - Boyd, Harold - Boyle, W. (Collective Folders: BOYD N-R; BOYD S-Z; BOYE; BOYL; BOYLE A-Z) (Box 0128)
    - Boyle, William - Braden, Thomas (Collective Folders: BOZ; BR; BRAC; BRAD) (Box 0129)
    - Braden, Vic - Bradley, Gen Omar N. (Collective Folders: BRADFORD A-Z; BRADLEY A-G; BRADLEY H-P) (Box 0130)
    - Bradley, Pat - Bragg (Collective Folders: BRADLEY R-Z; BRADS; BRADY A-I; BRADY J-Q; BRADY R-Z; BRAG) (Box 0131)
    - Bragno - Brando, Marlon (Collective Folders: BRAH; BRAI; BRAM; BRAN; BRANCH; BRAND; BRAND A-Z) (Box 0132)
    - Brando, Marlon - Branton (Collective Folders: BRANN; BRANS; BRANT; BRAS) (Box 0133)
    - Brasco - Breaux (Collective Folders: BRASS; BRATT; BRAU; BRAV; BRAY; BRE) (Box 0134)
    - Brecheen - Brennan, Walter (Collective Folders: BREC; BREE; BREG; BREN; BRENNAN A-Z) (Box 0135)
    - Brennan, William J. III - Brewer, Jim (Collective Folders: BRENNER A-Z; BRENT A-Z; BRET; BREW; BREWER A-Z) (Box 0136)
    - Brewer - Brezhnev, Leonid (Collective Folders: BREWSTER A-Z) (Box 0137)
      Brezhnev, leonard needs new label
    - Brezhnev, Leonid - Bricklen (Collective Folders: BRI; BRIC) (Box 0138)
    - Brickman - Briguglio (Collective Folders: BRID; BRIG; BRIGGS A-Z; BRIGH; BRIGHT A-Z; BRIL) (Box 0139)
    - Briles - Britt (Collective Folders: BRIM; BRIN; BRIS; BRIT; BRITT) (Box 0140)
    - Britten - Brodie (Collective Folders: BRO; BROAD; BROC; BROCK A-Z; BROD; BRODE; BRODI) (Box 0141)
    - Brodock - Bronson, Charles (Collective Folders: BRODS; BROE; BROG; BROK; BROM; BROML; BRON; BRONS) (Box 0142)
    - Bronson, Eugene - Brooks, Dick (Collective Folders: BROO; BROOK A-Z; BROOKE A-Z; BROOKS A-B; BROOKS C; BROOKS D-E) (Box 0143)
    - Brooks, Donald - Brosnan (Collective Folders: BROOKS F-G; BROOKS H; BROOKS I-O; BROOKS P; BROOKS Q-R; BROOKS S-Z; BROP; BROS; BROT) (Box 0144)
    - Brothers- Brown, Edmund (Collective Folders: BROU; BROW; BROWN; BROWN A; BROWN B; BROWN C; BROWN D; BROWN E) (Box 0145)
    - Brown, Edmund, Jr. - Brown, Georgia (Collective Folders: BROWN F; BROWN G) (Box 0146)
    - Brown, Gerald - Brown, Jim (Collective Folders: BROWN H; BROWN I; BROWN J) (Box 0147)
    - Brown, Jim - Brown, Pete (Collective Folders: BROWN K; BROWN L; BROWN M; BROWN N; BROWN O; BROWN P) (Box 0148)
    - Brown, Peter - Brown, Winthrop (Collective Folders: BROWN R; BROWN S; BROWN T; BROWN W; BROWNE) (Box 0149)
    - Browne - BROZ (Collective Folders: BROWNING; BROZ; BRU; BRU) (Box 0150)
    - Brubeck - Brundige (Collective Folders: BRUCE; BRUCE; BRUCK; BRUM; BRUN) (Box 0151)
    - Brunei - Bryant, Eugene (Collective Folders: BRUS; BRUT; BRY; BRYAN; BRYANT) (Box 0152)
    - Bryant, Paul - Buber (Collective Folders: BRZ; BT; BU; BUB) (Box 0153)
    - Bubnov - Bucher, Giovanni Enrico (Collective Folders: BUC; BUCH; BUCHANAN; BUCHE) (Box 0154)
    - Bucher, Lloyd - Buckson (Collective Folders: BUCK; BUCKI; BUCKL; BUCKM) (Box 0155)
    - Budd - Bujold (Collective Folders: BUD; BUE; BUF; BUG; BUH) (Box 0156)
    - Bukich- Bunche (Collective Folders: BUK; BUL; BULL; BUM; BUN) (Box 0157)
    - Bundy - Burch, Dean (Collective Folders: BUNKER; BUNT; BUR; BURC) (Box 0158)
    - Burch, Dean - Burgess, Carter L. (Collective Folders: BURD; BURE; BURG; BURGESS) (Box 0159)
    - Burgess, Isabel - Burke (Collective Folders: BURK; BURKE; BURKE A-E; BURKE H-J; BURKE K-O; BURKE P-Z) (Box 0160)
    - Burkett - Burnham (Collective Folders: BURKH; BURL; BURN; BURNETT A-Z; BURNETTE; BURNHAM; BURNS; BURNS A-F) (Box 0161)
    - Burns - Burnstan (Collective Folders: BURNS G-K; BURNS L-Z; BURR) (Box 0162)
    - Burr - Burtner (Collective Folders: BURRE; BURRI; BURROUGHS A-Z; BURROW; BURS; BURT; BURTON A-E) (Box 0163)
    - Burton - Bury (Collective Folders: BURTON F-P; BURTON R-Z; BUS) (Box 0164)
    - Busbee - Bush, George H.W. (Collective Folders: BUSC; BUSH A-J) (Box 0165)
    - Bush, George H.W. - Buthelezi (Collective Folders: BUSH K-O; BUSH P-Z; BUSS; BUST; BUT) (Box 0166)
    - Butkus - Butz, Earl (Collective Folders: BUTLER; BUTT; BUTTER; BUTTS A-Z; BUTZ) (Box 0167)
    - Butz, Earl - Byrd, Beverly (Collective Folders: BUX; BUZ; BY; BYE; BYI; BYR) (Box 0168)
    - Byrd, Beverley - Byrd, Robert C. (Box 0169)
    - Byrd, Robert C. - Byron, Goodloe E. (Box 0170)
    - Byron, Jeffrey - Caetano (Collective Folders: C; C; CAB; CAC; CAD; CAF) (Box 0171)
    - Cafego - Cahn (Collective Folders: CAG; CAH) (Box 0172)
    - Cahoon - Caldwell, George B. (Collective Folders: CAI; CAL; CALA; CALD; CALDWELL A-P) (Box 0173)
    - Caldwell, Capr. Henry H. - Calio (Collective Folders: CALDWELL Q-Z; CALHOUN A-G; CALHOUN J-Z; CALI; CALIO) (Box 0174)
    - Calkins - Calley (Collective Folders: CALK; CALL; CALLAGHAN A-Z; CALLAHAN A-Z; CALLAWAY A-Z) (Box 0175)
    - Calley, William Jr. - Cambodia- Royal Family (Collective Folders: CALLI; CALLO; CALO; CALV; CALVERT A-Z; CAM) (Box 0176)
    - Cambodia- Royal Family - Campbell, Bruce (Collective Folders: CAME; CAMERON; CAMI; CAMP; CAMP A-Z; CAMPBELL A; CAMPBELL B) (Box 0177)
    - Campbell, Clarence - Campbell, William (Collective Folders: CAMPBELL C; CAMPBELL D; CAMPBELL E; CAMPBELL F; CAMPBELL G; CAMPBELL H; CAMPBELL I; CAMPBELL J; CAMPBELL K; CAMPBELL L; CAMPBELL M; CAMPBELL N; CAMPBELL O; CAMPBELL P; CAMPBELL Q; CAMPBELL R; CAMPBELL S; CAMPBELL T; CAMPBELL U-V; CAMPBELL X-Z; CAMPE) (Box 0178)
    - Campfield - Cannon, Rep. Clarence Mo. (Collective Folders: CAN; CANA; CANFIELD; CANG; CANI; CANN; CANNE; CANNI; CANNON A-I) (Box 0179)
    - Cannon, J.D. - Capote, Truman (Collective Folders: CANNON J-R; CANNON S-Z; CANO; CANT; CANTI; CANTO; CANTR; CANU; CAO; CAP; CAPE; CAPL) (Box 0180)
    - Capozzoli - Cardenas (Collective Folders: CAPP; CAPR; CAPU; CAR; CARA; CARB; CARD) (Box 0181)
    - Cardin - Carli (Collective Folders: CARE; CAREY A-G; CAREY H-Q; CAREY R-Z; CARL; CARLE; CARLI) (Box 0182)
    - Carlin - Carmichael, Hoagy (Collective Folders: CARLO; CARLS; CARLT; CARLY; CARM) (Box 0183)
    - Carmichael, Ian - Caron (Collective Folders: CARN; CARNEY A-Z; CARO; CAROL; CARON) (Box 0184)
    - Carow - Carper (Collective Folders: CARP; CARPE; CARPENTER A-C; CARPENTER D; CARPENTER E-G; CARPENTER H-J; CARPENTER K-M; CARPENTER N-Q) (Box 0185)
    - Carr - Carradine, Keith (Collective Folders: CARR; CAR A-C; CARR D; CARR E-G; CARR H-L; CARR M-O; CARR P-Q; CARR S-Z; CARRA) (Box 0186)
    - Carradine, Rudolph - Carroll, Joseph (Collective Folders: CARRE; CARRI; CARRIL; CARRINGTON; CARROLL A-D; CAROLL E; CARROLL F-I; CARROLL J) (Box 0187)
    - Carroll, Julian M. - Carson, Mindy (Collective Folders: CARROLL K-L; CARROLL M; CARROLL N-R; CARROLL S-Z; CARS; CARSON A-J; CARSON K-P) (Box 0188)
    - Carson, Rachel L. (Author) - Carter, Amy (1979) (Collective Folders: CARSON Q-Z; CART; CARTER, A.) (Box 0189)
    - Carter, Amy (1980) - Carter, Billy (Mrs.) - Sybil (Collective Folders: CARTER, B.) (Box 0190)
    - Carter, Billy (Mrs.) - Carter, Jerome (Collective Folders: CARTER, C.; D; E; F; G; H; I; J) (Box 0191)
    - Carter, Jimmy (1977) - Carter, Jimmy (Campaign For President) (Collective Folders: CARTER, JIMMY ("ASK PRESIDENT CARTER")) (Box 0192)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Presidential Campaign - 1976) - Carter, Jimmy (Church) (Box 0193)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Conferences, Summit, Jan. 1979) - Carter, Jimmy (Gas Shortage) (Box 0194)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Gifts) - Carter, Jimmy (Offices) (Box 0195)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Paintings, Sculptures, Etc.) - Carter, Jimmy (Portraits-1980) (Box 0196)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Press Conferences 1977) - Carter, Jimmy, (Signing-1977-1978) (Box 0197)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Signings-1980) - Carter, Jimmy (Sports-General) (Box 0198)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Sports-Auto Racing) - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Belgium, 1978) (Box 0199)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Camp David) - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Germany, 1978) (Box 0200)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Guadeloupe) - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Middle East, 1979) incl. Israel and Egypt (Box 0201)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Military Academies) - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Virginia) (Box 0202)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Visits-Washington State) - Carter, Jimmy (With Athletes) (Box 0203)
    - Carter, Jimmy (With Begin, Menahem) - Carter, Jimmy (With Crowds) (Box 0204)
    - Carter, Jimmy (With Cubans) - Carter, Jimmy (With Kings and Queens) (Box 0205)
    - Carter, Jimmy (With Kissinger, Henry) - Carter, Jimmy (With Prime Ministers, 1977) (Box 0206)
    - Carter, Jimmy (With Princes and Princesses) - Carter, Jimmy (Mrs. Rosalyn) (Box 0207)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Mrs. - 1979) - Carter, Jimmy (Mrs. - Visits, Latin America 1977) (Collective Folders: CARTER, K.; CARTER, L.) (Box 0208)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Mrs. - Visits, Thailand) - Carter, Lillian (Box 0209)
    - Carter, Lillian - Carvin, Michael (Collective Folders: CARTER, M; N; O; P-Q; R; S; T; U-V; W; X-Z; CARTWRIGHT; CARU; CARV) (Box 0210)
    - Carwile, Howard W. (Richmond Councilman) - Casey, Robert (Representative, D-TX) (Collective Folders: CARY; CAS; CASA; CASEY) (Box 0211)
    - Casey, Robert - Cassavetes, John (Collective Folders: CASH; CASK; CASP; CASS; CASS A-Z; CASSA; CASSE) (Box 0212)
    - Cassell, Charles - Casto, Harold J. (Collective Folders: CASSIDY A-Z; CAST; CASTE; CASTI; CASTLE) (Box 0213)
    - Castro, Fidel (Cuba) - Castro, Fidel (Visits - US - 1979) (Box 0214)
    - Castro, Fidel (1974) - Caulfield, John J. (Collective Folders: CASTR; CASW; CAT; CATE; CATH; CATL; CATR; CATT; CAU) (Box 0215)
    - Caulfield, Lore - Cayton, Judge Nathen (Collective Folders: CAV; CAVA; CAVE; CAW; CAY; CAZ; CE) (Box 0216)
    - Ceausescu, Nicolae - Cernik, Oldrich (Collective Folders: CEC; CEL; CEN; CER) (Box 0217)